[
  {
    "question": "2 + 3?",
    "answer_a": "4",
    "answer_b": "5",
    "answer_c": "6",
    "answer_d": "8",
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "9 - 5?",
    "answer_a": "4",
    "answer_b": "2",
    "answer_c": "1",
    "answer_d": "7",
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "3 * 3?",
    "answer_a": "4",
    "answer_b": "10",
    "answer_c": "9",
    "answer_d": "3",
    "correct_answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "10 / 5?",
    "answer_a": "3",
    "answer_b": "0",
    "answer_c": "6",
    "answer_d": "2",
    "correct_answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "2 + 3?",
    "answer_a": "4",
    "answer_b": "5",
    "answer_c": "6",
    "answer_d": "8",
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "6 * 2?",
    "answer_a": "24",
    "answer_b": "5",
    "answer_c": "15",
    "answer_d": "12",
    "correct_answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "10 + 4?",
    "answer_a": "14",
    "answer_b": "5",
    "answer_c": "6",
    "answer_d": "18",
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },{
    "question": "10 * 0?",
    "answer_a": "10",
    "answer_b": "15",
    "answer_c": "100",
    "answer_d": "0",
    "correct_answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "13 + 3?",
    "answer_a": "14",
    "answer_b": "5",
    "answer_c": "16",
    "answer_d": "10",
    "correct_answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "12 / 3?",
    "answer_a": "4",
    "answer_b": "10",
    "answer_c": "9",
    "answer_d": "8",
    "correct_answer": "A"
  }
]